Is it fun for you to come over and do
some of these like more
runnable races after like
all the mountain stuff that you're doing
or is it kind of like a is it more of a
challenge do you find?
I get the right song. Yeah. The only part
that I have really run is other Molly's
cousin lives in Auburn and so.
Yeah so. Yeah so we posted up. Yeah and
it's beautiful like
the back. I'm excited for
mile 62 on. That's what my. Yeah I
think it's yeah it
really fits there because it's
kind of flat. I mean it's just very
mellow up and downs or so on
the heat and yeah no it's yeah.
Yeah do you have any tips for? Fun. For
you John. Yeah I see. So
no and this really don't
feel that it will be too hot. So I think
that's it. It was
yeah feels like it's one
less thing to worry about. Kind of
better. Yeah I'm not too
too much of a care or too
much the heat and that. Yeah I feel like
you've like made all
these like cooling strategies.
Yeah it's like you and Lesnar kind of.
Yeah. They're not big. Like do I need to
wear like a jacket or
something? Yeah the starting looks like
yeah like 40 degrees or something like
that. Yeah so who knows.
No it would be but yeah it's yeah I think
but I think it's the
same like I haven't run ever
like from milestone but probably the same
feeling of like the last
kilometers that you feel like
that you are really working now. Yeah
that you need to just keep
on the pain. Yeah exactly. So
it's only that here is just like a bit
longer. Well and I think
that's how I'm trying to approach
and my health just kind of having me.
It's just different because
I feel like in a marathon you
treat that like you treat mile 18 is like
okay the racing really
starts. Yeah. Like here it seems
like the racing really starts around 62.
I know. Yeah exactly. It's
like but it's the same feeling
of like exactly. It's just gonna hurt the
last part. You're just
going. Yeah and probably here
the thing is that you feel super easy
like you are doing a jog.
Like you are oh that's so easy.
That's so easy. You are just jogging. You
can be chatting and then
in a moment you stop like
chatting. Yeah. And you feel like I'm
running like very slow but yeah I'm
working out and then you
need to keep going and it's that's I
think that's kind of the beauty also of
long distance that you
are never running fast but but you see
that this low speed your
body is like getting warm,
getting warm. Yeah. Yeah. Is it fun for
you to come over and
do some of these like
more runnable races after like all the
mountain stuff that you're
doing or is it kind of like a
is it more of a challenge do you find?
Yeah it feels more the
challenge and that's what is
exciting not like to do something that it
doesn't necessarily fit me.
Yeah. To do something yeah that
it's more runnable than I need to think
more about depending and the thing is
that I will not usually
yeah yeah yeah. When did you thought
about like doing like
Western, or did it come like
just straight like the marathon or did
you take some time? No it
like I feel like things have
evolved so much over the last year like I
had I'd really messed up
my knees marathoning like I
couldn't run for a while. Like, I broke my
kneecap training in the
beginning of 2024. Yeah and so
I was out of the the 2024 Olympics and I
didn't run for most of that
year and I was kind of like I
wasn't sure if I was going to be done
because like to be honest like 30 years
old is kind of getting
up there for marathoning at this point
and luckily I like I
took the whole year of that
my body kind of calmed down let the
inflammation calm down but road running
was still like incredibly
painful on my knees and basically through
just like running around
Flagstaff meeting new people
and kind of seeing like trail running was
the one thing that was kind
of saving it. Yeah. And so
naturally just started doing more trail
running around where I was
and got linked up with the
coach that I work with now and basically
used it as an avenue to be
like hey I still want to keep
doing this I just don't know how I can
make it work still on the
roads and seeing that there's
like this whole side of the sport that
allows me to keep doing it
and so I like obviously it sucks
to have injuries and things that you
don't plan for but I think I wouldn't
have been pushed into
something like I really enjoy doing this
and I think it's really
given me kind of this new lease
on like my career but I wouldn't have
necessarily found it if I hadn't been
pushed into injuries
on the road because marathoning it's just
so hard on your body. Yeah
like I feel it now I ran New
York City Marathon last November and I
actually had to drop out
because it was just like my knees
couldn't handle it but it is cool to be
like I don't know to be
able to go and have my my body
be able to handle 62 plus miles is really
kind of like a revelation of
like I was in a place where I
didn't think I'd ever be able to run like
even a marathon distance.
Yeah and to see that then you
made it to like a hundred miles. Yeah, and
even I questioned a lot too
like when I dropped out in
New York at 18 I'm like man like I just
don't know if my body can
handle distance anymore maybe
that is kind of just it and so that's why
I think I've really enjoyed
this so much because like I
love running and I love just getting to
like see what my body could
do. Yeah I know I think that's
yeah I feel like the last years that they
have been running a bit more
like on flat just to prepare
races like this. Yeah yeah. That I
started much more on the like
joints and that, compared
like I could be doing like 60 hours no
nonstop in the mountains, no
program. Yeah. But then like
running like the monotony of the cadence
and the impact on the
pavement. Like, yeah, it's so different
for all the joints
and that it's so much more
about sports. Yeah it just
gets your body in different ways but I
think that is what's cool
about running is there's so many
facets of the sport that like. Yeah it's
not only one thing that you
just do like yeah. Yeah but I
think that's what I love too like I come
from like a track background being like
that's how I started
like the area that I'm from is not trails
not mountains and hill and
so it is fun to be able to
like rediscover different parts of it through
that. Did you come like a
did you have a family culture
about running and that's what you got to
do. Oh my god oh yeah
Sure. No, like, my parents still
don't like my parents have been actively
being like, a hundred
miles is too far. Why have you
done it? Exactly. But my mom said
the same thing when I went to run my
first marathon at 25
and saw so it's like for them it's been a
very steep learning curve.
Yeah but I don't know they
were always like supportive of it they
just do not understand it.
Yeah yeah but it was more of like
just knowing that I really wanted to do
it rather than like I don't
know, I had to kind of work it
all out myself. Yeah. Where did
the idea of running come from?
like it was from a school like
after that. We ran a lot in school yeah
but I would even just like
go out and do it by myself
like we lived um like we live in a very
like flat part of like northern US
Wisconsin and like we
had woods up behind the house and I'd
just go there myself and run but yeah I
feel like it came from
that of just like enjoying being out and
that's why like this is really cool
because it's kind of
just an extension of that of like just
getting to be outside for a
really long time. Yeah no it's
yeah that connection to the landscape.
Yeah but I don't
necessarily it's so funny now of like
I only grew up on like non-technical
terrain and so now it's like some of the
stuff I'm like oh my
god or even like I got to go out to um uh
Chamonix earlier in the year
and see at night that was the
first time I ran the trails in Chamonix. I
was like, oh, European
trails are very technical
or like I see some of this yeah I see
some of the stuff that you
do in here on like the side of
the mountain like climbing I'm like oh
god no yeah you don't want
to be there no like that's
a different kind of sport yeah but that I
think that's the fun or like
for me the cool thing about
running like mountain running and that is
that it's it can be so wild
like from like a race that
it's uh I don't know like like Sonoma for
example or that that is very
flat and runnable, and people
run fast, to something a bit more
extreme. It's, uh, and
it's time still like the same
sport the same activity but yeah yeah and
you can like transition
from one to the other depending
on what you want to do at the moment for
sure yeah yeah it's uh yeah do you have
any like I feel like
you've always got like a crazy adventure
like going out like do you
have anything planned for
after this or for the rest of the year is
he getting me mostly
like what are you saying
not not this year and most is because
like um uh the last two
years they have been doing like
long projects like that they did last
year in the US, the one before in the
Alps and and it's very
time demanding uh for uh for me but
doesn't for like my wife and
and because then like when I'm
away then she's uh with the kids and even
if like it's a matter
of someone coming like
kids it's it's very time yeah for sure
and uh actually and now
after the pregnancy, she's
getting back into racing shape. So we plan more
like okay with races this
year so it's yeah easy like
logistically so uh we can like uh do both
of us like uh racing and
uh yeah it's kind of more
logistics-wise. Yeah, like doing
things also like uh adventure it's no
that's fun how old are
your kids they are seven five and one so
yeah it's still like very
good busy yeah yeah have they
busy. Yeah. Do they get out in the mountains? Like, do
you guys take them on
adventures or do they kind of
want to like do their own thing yeah no
it's fun that like they they know
competition because like
uh we both race and then we have a lot of
friends like uh i don't know
you're a new song that you're
running here she's a good friend and the
neighbor are like yeah it's
it's uh it's a we have a few
friends that they are racing a lot where
we lead and then for them
is like kind of grown-ups to
that the races are just part of it.
But where we live, it's
not like they really know what
racing is. Yeah, but we go a lot
outside like they love to go
to they to the mountains and
climb but yeah they can walk a lot like
they can take five hours walks in the
mountains oh my gosh
easily, no problem. So yes, they love
that but yeah we will see
they what they want to do
but they think it's more like we want
that to appreciate to the
outdoors yeah i think that's
outdoors. Yeah, I think that's what it's for. Whether they want to race
or not, that's secondary.
yeah i feel like that's got
to be hard like coming from like a pro
running background of like
whether or not like you want
them to like get into competition early
or not no the pressure that
they can feel like uh like
yeah seeing that and that's something
that um i could say for
example with my sister that
she was racing like uh but she's two
years younger than me and then like she
would feel the pressure
like i was winning versus so everybody's
party yeah and like uh with
the kids probably the same
so like if we can keep them like yeah
yeah from that they never
get to just be like normal days
and that they're always going to have
like you as their dad yeah
no so that's something that we
already want to separate like how invite
yeah i think that's fair
yeah how do you feel the
pressure like uh it's uh different like
uh i'm sure that it's very
different pressure like on
like going to uh olympic games oh to here
but uh yeah you've been
like i think one of the
because I know a lot of athletes who are
are very good at this
but they they don't perform
on the big days because and i think it's
that's race
management and pain management.
yeah but uh how do you feel like the
difference it's interesting i
think some of like especially
for when i was racing tokyo or like doing
these big road marathons i'd
feel so much pressure almost
like it was almost like a consuming
amount of like anxiety before races
because they were really big
stages and it was like really really high
stakes with stuff and not
that this is any less high of
stakes like i actually think no no but
you you have that day that
and you have expectations that
they might be super high and yeah and
it's that that i think there's
something to put whether it's
a marathon whether it's 100 miles with
these long distance events
you put in so many months of
preparation for one day or same thing
for Tokyo, you put in
four years of preparation for one
day and having that experience of like
one of them going really well and then
the opposite happening
in 2024 where it's like prepare and
prepare and then everything like goes to
shit before you even
get to the line i think i learned to
maybe be a little bit more
not like chill out with the
expectations but at the very least remind
myself that like the only
thing you can control is like
your preparation your attitude there's
nothing like trying to like
push harder control you know
not control the outcome exactly like then
what's gonna happen is gonna
happen, and it's out of us. Yeah.
and yeah it's other people to like
sometimes be focused too much yeah but
it's hard because it's
like you want to be able to control the
outcome and have this
attitude of like oh if i just work
a little bit harder then it can happen
but i think that that just naturally
happens in the race like
there's there's almost this thing that
comes over you when you're having a
really good race that it
feels like outside of you so it's like i
think some of it is just
learning to trust a little bit
that like i trust that i'm gonna know
what i need to do in the race when i'm
like i'm gonna have a
lot of afterwards or not tomorrow but
like yeah i don't know i
think it is just comes with like
being a little bit older and having done
this for a while but i don't
know i feel like there's always
going to be pressure like yeah and i
think that that's also it
means that it's mean for probably
if it's not any pressure before like when
it's probably not
meaningful like yes yeah so that's
uh yeah yeah and even this year it's like
it's fun being into position
where like i think coming in
as a little bit of an outsider here like
yeah there's
expectations but at the same time
people are like, oh, you're from the
roads. It's a
little bit of being able to
to like play within the expectations a
bit and maybe that'll change
as in the sport longer like
i think it's very different for someone
like you coming out where it's like
you've got this long
history of trail running yeah where it's
history of trail running. Yeah, whereas
at Black Canyon,
ever ultra people are like oh it's cool
she does well and if not
like who cares yeah and so that
that's kind of nice because on the roads
i can't show up to a race
without being a medalist and
that is hard yeah i think it's um it's
just it's a very sweet
spot, like when you're starting
something and you have internal
expectations but uh but you don't have a
fear of um of failure
kind of like because you you are not like
uh that you are like i
want to really progress and
try to win the races but but uh if you
are not winning you will
not feel the same kind of failure.
and then it comes a moment where like you
are expecting to win and
everything but winning it
feels like a failure yeah and and at some
point it switches from
like being exciting to win
or just winning it just like a relief
yeah yeah that's a very it's
sad yeah it switches from that
like it just like you said like the
excitement to race versus
like the fear of losing yet and i
think when you approach things with that
fear then everything becomes harder
because you almost like
stiffen up because you're afraid to make
a mistake yeah whereas like i know i'm
gonna make a bunch of
mistakes in this i mean a bunch of
mistakes at black canyon
but the fun part is getting to
like know that i'm gonna have to figure
out things within the race, and learning
about those yeah as the
fun part like think of doing a sport is
about living and
progressing yeah no it was great like
one of my best friends called me this
morning and she i had a
conversation with her before my first
marathon as well where she was like just
like, really savor
being a rookie at something.
yeah and i'm like it's really cool that i
get to do that again of
like i'm never gonna get to run
the first hundred miler again yeah
remembering like this is a
really special thing and you don't
get opportunities like this often yeah no
i think yeah yeah your
management being the first time to
do something it's always yeah so so
powerful yeah and and and it's like a kid
like you feel like a
kid not like oh it's it's exploration
yeah yeah that's exploring
the emotions and and all that
yeah yeah yeah even just the aspect that
there's so many more things
that go into racing like this
then like a marathon is so systematic
yeah basically it's it
almost feels more like how
cycling or like road cycling yeah and you
have a plan and you need to
execute and everything it's
like your new trajectory based exactly
off of like each 5k and like it's i mean
two and a half hours
is like pretty short it's you're just
like click click click click click but
he's probably exactly
like i'm a fly like and just yeah i have
no idea like what's gonna
happen and so it's that of
being like okay you can be a little bit
more flexible with it
and being able to use that
aspect of like oh i love races that are
really tough conditions
because you have to kind of like
figure out on the fly yeah yeah you know
i think yeah you overt it
like doesn't arrive i think so
that and um uh it's felt like to when
talking with uh like
yeah at least i'm done that
i seem like uh many people like from from
outside like they think
about a lot of us like
the training that uh that we are doing or
like nutrition or that but
uh i think the the mental
aspect of the athletes who
success it's it's so
underrated yeah and it is such a big
i think uh like the the resilience into
all these problems that
you because like yeah it's
your performance is your body and it's uh
um yeah you are always questioning
yourself and everything
that you are doing day after day and and
and that the resilience i think on the
brain and and on the
uh on on the races um yeah i how uh how
have you been working that
is something natural for you
like uh yeah because also like yeah you
had big success on injuries and then like
because it's it's never linear like oh no
no and that i think that
was the hardest thing to like
especially coming into this like having
to basically start from
like zero with my running
like when i started building up for these
kinds of races like i
couldn't run more than a mile or two
and so i think that there was a big
aspect of having to like
almost like relearn those
aspects of training and just like callus
my brain so because like it
training is hard it's really
mentally difficult um but i think the
toughest aspect but i think the thing
that matters the most
for me was that like road running for me
it's like not easy per se
but like i know that world
really really well and like a marathon
workout is very hard in a
very specific way but you're not
failing very often it's very like
moderate moderately hard
levels of work all the time
and with trail running especially with
some of these longer runs
or just doing stuff in the
mountains i was so bad at it like a reach
like when i started doing
it and i just failed so often
and that aspect of just like having to
deal like with coming up on
your own limits all the time
i don't think i realized how like how
mentally strong that would
make me over and over because
you have to like learn to just be like
okay like shit's really hard
and i'm just gonna like keep
doing it anyway like i don't know the
number of times i feel like
i'd finish a training run and
I'd finish a training run and
just feel deeply defeated. Even like,
girlfriend just like the number of
times i come home just be like i don't
think i can do this i had a
run in the grand canyon that
was like one of the most demoralizing
runs i've ever done i was like i don't
know if i'm gonna be
able to do a hundred mile race if i can't
finish this but it's that
aspect of just like being
totally defeated and be like well i'm
gonna come back tomorrow and
do it again like i think that
that that was really really cool to just
see how like how resilient
my own brain and body could be
but i think that only comes through
training and that's why i do love this
sport because nothing
else in my life is this hard like and not
that like running like this
is a very specific kind of
like curated hard there are very hard
things in life but i think that
opportunity to like have to
really confront your own weaknesses all
the time is like a really special
experience yeah it's
it's like a big mirror exactly like put
yourself there and you need
to really accept who you are
like who you are yeah you need to take
off all the mess that you
have and he's like okay yeah
that's me the real me i cannot hide it
and it is so i need to confront my
weaknesses and you really
do have to confront all the time like the
weakest most selfish like
pitiful parts of yourself
because you just spend so much time in
your own head and like i
think that's been really cool
like you almost like redevelop your
relationship with yourself because you
spend so much time with
yourself and you can't like gaslight your
way out of it it's like if
you quit a run early like
there's no one to blame but yourself. Yeah.
no and it's not uh it's
it's not that you are like
putting things in your backpack and then
you own that it's like
every time, every race that
you start you you start from from zero
it's not because you have
been winning all that that you
are already on that position it's like
you need to confront yourself
every time and and see that so
that's uh that's the cool thing about
the sport. And I
think that's what the sport is too. Yeah.
is that but uh yeah do you feel like like
obviously you've been
racing in really high
level on trails for a very long
time at this point. Do
you feel like you're still
learning things about yourself like or do
you feel like you've kind of like
gotten to know yourself a little bit? Because
i remember as a kid like
like reading your books
watching your races and stuff like that
where it's like i think
it's that like it seems like
you've been really dialed in on this for
a really long time but i
also know that i fall into that
same trap that like i have people that
look at me and go, oh, you
must be dialed in. Like, I have
nothing dialed. And then we evolve
to like it's uh and now
i'm i i'm learning about
all those things like i'm i'm aging so
like it's things that i
wasn't worried at all before like
on the i don't know all the neuromuscular
power like it wasn't you
are young you go running you
go back and you are fine and now it's
like some things i'm so
much dialed and i don't need to
think about because uh that but another
things i need to learn
again like uh you like uh both
things to to perform at the same level
it's it's just like your
body's evolving so you need to
to change also like what you yeah to
learn all the time and and
then i think like also like
probably like it's the same for you like
to come to ultras, you
are discovering new one new
new limitations or things to overcome.
i with for me it's more
like this project when going to
the mountains it's like okay that's i
don't know how to solve these problems
and how to do it and
then it's very interesting on that but uh
i think it's like doing if
you do exactly the same thing
all the time even like your body's
changing so you are always like in need
of of dialing things
and trying to to understand how it works
and it's uh and uh yeah
it's like not every day is like
the one before. So then, as
you mentioned like you
can have an injury and then
you need to run with that, or like the whole
year like i don't know
it's uh life changed all the
time so it's not that you have something
dialed and like it's okay
that's my training plan and i
will it worked this year for me so i will
repeat it exactly every
time yeah it's not working like
that like you need to adapt it and and
and yeah adapting to
everything is changing on the
circumstances yeah that's the no i i
totally feel that and agree like i think
that's it if you try
to keep like replicating the same thing
over and over like you like maybe a
training plan worked
for that period of time or like where in
your life you are but you
almost have to like keep
growing and evolving and if you keep
trying to just repeat it it's not ever
going to like work in the
same way yeah yeah exactly yeah yeah yeah
it is kind of wild i feel
like the the process of like
getting older in a sport and like
learning and growing but
also trying to be like, oh,
i can't train like the way that i used to
but at the same time like i
feel like i'm much stronger
and i'm like i could never train like how
i did when i was like 25
and training for the marathon
but at the same time i'm like glad that i
don't have to do that
anymore because i know so much
more about my body that like i get to
train in different ways that
like maybe a little bit more
sustainable, or lead to
different outcomes but
it's cool it's always like
experimentation yeah and i think it's uh
they're like yeah training
is a way to experiment with
your body and some things that you you
have a cure like you
don't need to work it anymore
if i don't yeah you need to do it on on
now and changing on the this
body i think in growth it's
very yeah did you start like the short
distance and more yeah yeah it was
started like basically
I used to do the mile. I did the
mile and two mile in high school was
basically 3k through
10k in college and then after college
yeah i switched early but
just because i i trained
like a psychopath when i was in college
like in a way that like he's
both should not train like that
but i didn't know any better that was
just the nature of like
how i was taught to like be
successful but it was in a way that like
my coach would push me to do
but wasn't meant for long term
stability it was meant to like win a lot
of NCAA
championships um and i had to really
learn over time like what sustainable
training looks like
because even now like i think my
experience of training for Tokyo was like
i was able to maintain that
level of training for like
two years before i broke and then trying
to replicate it in 2024
i didn't make it to the
start line and so so much of this is kind
of wild of approaching
ultramarathon training away
that i'm like okay it is objectively like
much farther but i train
in a way that like my body
feels better because like i can't keep
breaking like that you can
only break your bones some
age, and you're like, I don't want to
go through that again.
none and i think um we have
been taught so much about like high level
it's it's not sustainable
like it's you need to push
your body to the limits and and and and
it's uh like we don't look
for health you will look for
performance and to understand that the
the maximum performance is the maximum
expression of health
like if we have all our systems our body
like as healthy as possible
is where we will be able to
perform the best but we are not often
told like that is like no
you need to really push through
it like i think it's almost like it's too
different approaches to
sport because it's like
i feel like that's the that's the side of
the sport that i'm trying
to experiment with because
like the side of the sport that i had
come from it was very much like being
told like if you like
you as your healthiest self are not your
fastest self. And it's hard, like,
unprogramming all of
that because like all of my experience
has been like you have to basically
sacrifice your mental
health your physical health and you're
gonna achieve it but like
you're gonna come out short
time like if a year's change a little for
like short time and then
not anymore and even that
aspect of like achieving something big
but feeling really empty on the other
side a bit just because
it's like yeah winning is really cool but
it really sucks to know
that like you had to sacrifice
everything about yourself to get that
thing and i think that that's
that's why I enjoy where I am in my
career because i know at this point i'm
like the health kind of
comes first and if you can't come
out the other side like a better version
of yourself there
really isn't a whole point to
winning like i might never win this race
but it like to me i think
it matters more that i get to
like stay in the sport be sustainable
like you get to like continually run
rather than just like
hit it big and then be broken for a
couple years but i think it
took me like it took me a really
long time to come to that place i
remember being like 21 years old and
telling my coach i'm like i
don't care if i can't walk at age 40 i
want to win and that's
always that's that's like a
psychopathic way to be in the sport but
like i think it's easy
to say that when you're 20
you can't imagine what it feels like to
be older.
yeah on a ring yeah i have
when I was like 18, 19 years old,
I had a manifesto in my room. It was like
keys or gear it was like uh yeah like
basically like destroy your
body until like uh until you
are bleeding like uh the only thing that
is winning the race not
like you need to die to
it's like yeah like uh when you are maybe
when you're you're
like you need these extra
aspirational thing to put
yourself into the pain of
the training and the after is
like you understand that maybe you don't
need it but probably some
period like you have this
vision it it helps even if it's not
healthy in the wrong time uh so we are
having some i think that
is kind of like part of the life cycle of
yeah it's like though that
it's like when you're young
like that i think that level of like over
training like pushing
really hard comes from like a
fundamental insecurity of being like oh i
don't know if i'm that good
so i have to give everything
i have and i think as you get older you
trust a little bit more
like i trust that my body if
i treat it well is going to show up when
i need it to show up and so
i don't feel the need to like
squeeze the life out of it like I used to.
laugh that yeah no and that's
the thing i tell you of your
athletes all the time i'm like don't like
push like don't destroy
yourself don't push too hard
but then i'm like i would have never
listened to that like you have to it's
the kind of thing that
you have to like learn it yeah yeah i
think the only bad part
about that is that and especially
thing, if you're successful when you're
young, the hard part is that
you build your identity a lot
about the results. And I think if you are
probably if you are not very
successful then you you build
identity on many other things but if you
are just pushing on this
mindset and on that and you are
having the results and when you are like
in your teens or twenties, like all
your identity is built on that.
just like yeah after the injury i think
that's a hard thing yeah
I'm a marathoner. I'm this, I'm
that. That's what defines me. But
i'm like it's no in reality
you are much more than that
yeah but it's easy to say it but
internally i think it's fair
to believe it yeah but i think
even just like it's like that cliche like
like the more people you
have around you i think the more
you realize that like i think there's
that fear yeah when you're
successfully young and you're
like oh if i don't keep winning like
nobody's gonna like no
one's gonna hang around me and
then there's that realization of like oh
most of the people don't care
like your kids probably don't
care one bit how you're doing in this race.
like they're probably
just stoked that you're gonna
get back home like yeah and i think
that's uh yeah we we
sometimes put too much pressure
on a race, thinking it's very
important at the end of the
day yeah like oh this is just
a race like this is gonna be by any fire
race. Some fans may
say shit, but who cares
about it? Yeah, we're having some fun. Well,
I hope you have an amazing race on Saturday.
Man, I hope you have a good one too. I'll be
cheering for you there.
and yeah have a good day and
embrace it yeah it's just like beautiful
like the sunrise when
you go to the Escarpment, and
on the on the phone at the end like it's
something that yeah it could
be the first time running a
a race like it's uh some things that uh
yeah it's they are unique
so yeah i'm really excited to
just like experience it all i think it's
at that it's like it's
gonna be really cool i know it's
gonna be probably the hardest thing i've
ever done but like i
think being able to savor that
experience of like i've wanted to run
Western States since I was a
kid like this is pretty cool
yeah yeah well best of luck thanks so
much going air freezing it i still got
yeah oh my god it just
was great getting to
come over yeah no thanks